<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Electrade | Electric Vehicle Insurance</title>
    <link>https://electrade.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Electrade | Electric Vehicle Insurance</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://electrade.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Tesla Insurance 2019</title>
      <link>https://electrade.app/blog/best-tesla-insurance-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrade.app/blog/best-tesla-insurance-2019/</guid>
      <description>What is the problem with insuring Teslas, anyway? Many freshly-minted Tesla owners are getting quotes that are way higher than for similarly-valued ICE cars, while others are getting quotes that are lower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which EVs are cheapest to insure in California in 2019?</title>
      <link>https://electrade.app/blog/which-evs-are-cheapest-to-insure-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrade.app/blog/which-evs-are-cheapest-to-insure-2019/</guid>
      <description>Background Many Chevy Bolts, Tesla Model 3s, Nissan Leafs and similar are getting way higher quotes than
So which are cheapest to insure? So here are some prices from the field for 2019 - the 10 cheapest electric cars to insure in 2019 in California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why the time is right for EV auto insurance specialists</title>
      <link>https://electrade.app/blog/why-we-specialize-in-ev-auto-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrade.app/blog/why-we-specialize-in-ev-auto-insurance/</guid>
      <description>Just bought a new electric car and need to get car insurance? Take a look at our top tips to help you find the best deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Tesla Commercials and Ads so far</title>
      <link>https://electrade.app/blog/best-tesla-commercials-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrade.app/blog/best-tesla-commercials-so-far/</guid>
      <description>Why the shareholder meeting brought ads to the center again At the shareholder meeting yesterday 3+ shareholders mentioned the amount of disinformation around on the web regarding Tesla, and how maybe it was time to re-think the company&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;We don&amp;rsquo;t make ads – happy customers are the best marketing&amp;rdquo; stance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Insurance 2019 Update from Shareholder Meeting</title>
      <link>https://electrade.app/blog/tesla-insurance-update-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrade.app/blog/tesla-insurance-update-2019/</guid>
      <description>Tesla&amp;rsquo;s shareholder meeting is ongoing, but we wanted to update our readers in the meantime with the newest on Tesla Insurance, as we know from experience that this is a pain point for a lot of Tesla and EV owners out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are electric cars more expensive to insure in 2019?</title>
      <link>https://electrade.app/blog/are-electric-cars-more-expensive-to-insure-in-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrade.app/blog/are-electric-cars-more-expensive-to-insure-in-2019/</guid>
      <description>Many freshly-minted or experienced EV owners are getting quotes that are way higher than for similarly-valued ICE cars, while others are getting quotes that are lower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A list of the Best Electric Auto Insurance Companies for 2019</title>
      <link>https://electrade.app/blog/best-electric-auto-insurance-companies-in-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrade.app/blog/best-electric-auto-insurance-companies-in-2019/</guid>
      <description>Whether you&amp;rsquo;re in California, Massachusetts, Washington, Colorado, Rhode Island or New York – you&amp;rsquo;ve surely heard about how electric vehicle insurance can cost more. Luckily, it can also cost less if you play your cards right and explain to your agent the benefits of insuring an electric car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How insurance companies price electric car insurance</title>
      <link>https://electrade.app/blog/how-insurance-companies-price-electric-car-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrade.app/blog/how-insurance-companies-price-electric-car-insurance/</guid>
      <description>We often get asked how insurance companies price electric car (or any automobile) insurance policies. They don&amp;rsquo;t invent the numbers, but go down a predefined checklist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why EV insurance should cost less than normal car insurance</title>
      <link>https://electrade.app/blog/why-electric-vehicle-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrade.app/blog/why-electric-vehicle-insurance/</guid>
      <description>Your average electric car will have more advanced safety features than your average gas powered car and is therefore cheaper to insure. Nevertheless, if you&amp;rsquo;re not careful your insurance premium could actually be higher than for a comparable combustion car.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How much does electric car insurance actually cost in 2019?</title>
      <link>https://electrade.app/blog/how-much-is-electric-car-insurance-in-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://electrade.app/blog/how-much-is-electric-car-insurance-in-2019/</guid>
      <description>There is a lot of disinformation out there that electric cars are more expensive than ICE vehicles to insure. A lot of this FUD (fear, uncertainty and doubt) is most likely spread by comapanies wanting electric cars to fail.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>